A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1951
  - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/331.E
    - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3579)
  - El Salvador, 1951; 02.1951/333
    - Salvador, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Dominican Republic, 1951; 02.1951/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Dominican Republic - Malaria, 1951; 02.1951/335.I
    - Dominican Republic, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Uruguay, 1951; 02.1951/337
    - Uruguay, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/337.E
    - Uruguay, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Venezuela, 1951; 02.1951/339
    - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
  - Venezuela - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/339.C
    - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
  - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/339.E
    - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
  - Venezuela - Yellow Fever, 1951; 02.1951/339.O
    - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
  - Great Britain, 1951; 02.1951/400
    - Great Britain, 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3582)
  - England, 1951; 02.1951/401
    - England - (A-H), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3583)
    - England - (A-H), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3584)
    - England - Huxley, Julian, 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3585)
    - England - (I-01), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3586)
    - England - (I-01), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3587)
    - England - Oxford - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3588)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3589)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3590)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3591)
    - England - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3592)
    - England - (T-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/401.A
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/401.C
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/401.E
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Public Health Education, 1951; 02.1951/401.L
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/401.R
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - England - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/401.S
    - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - Scotland, 1951; 02.1951/405
    - Scotland - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3594)
    - Scotland - Scott, Jerome F., 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3666)
  - Scotland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 02.1951/405.D
    - Scotland, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3595)
  - Scotland - Social Services, 1951; 02.1951/405.S
    - Scotland, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3595)
  - Australia, 1951; 02.1951/410
    - Australia - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3596)
    - Australia - Australian National University - Pacific Studies, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3667)
  - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/410.A
    - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Australia - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/410.C
    - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/410.E
    - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/410.R
    - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Australia - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/410.S
    - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - New Zealand, 1951; 02.1951/418
    - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/418.A
    - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - New Zealand - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/418.C
    - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Caribbean, 1951; 02.1951/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3598)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3599)
  - Guyana, 1951; 02.1951/423
    - British Guyana, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3600)
  - Canada, 1951; 02.1951/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3600)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3601)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3602)
  - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/427.A
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Canada - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/427.C
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/427.E
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/427.R
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Canada - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/427.S
    - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Jamaica, 1951; 02.1951/437
  - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/437.A
    - Jamaica, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Trinidad, 1951; 02.1951/451
    - Trinidad, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka, 1951; 02.1951/462
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/462.C
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/462.E
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka - Malaria, 1951; 02.1951/462.I
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/462.S
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Hong Kong, 1951; 02.1951/463
    - Hong Kong, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - India, 1951; 02.1951/464
    - India - (General) - (A-B), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3605)
    - India - (C-H), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3606)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3607)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3608)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3609)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3610)
  - India - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/464.A
    - India, 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3611)
  - India - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/464.C
    - India, 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3611)
  - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 02.1951/464.D
    - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/464.E
    - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - India - Malaria, 1951; 02.1951/464.I
    - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - India - Yellow Fever, 1951; 02.1951/464.O
    - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - India - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/464.R
    - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - Pakistan, 1951; 02.1951/465
    - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Pakistan - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/465.A
    - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Pakistan - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/465.C
    - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Burma, 1951; 02.1951/468
  - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/468.R
    - Burma, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Iraq, 1951; 02.1951/470
    - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Iraq - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/470.E
    - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Iraq - Social Services, 1951; 02.1951/470.S
    - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - New Guinea, 1951; 02.1951/472
    - New Guinea, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Malaysia, 1951; 02.1951/473
    - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/473.A
    - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Malaysia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/473.R
    - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Africa, 1951; 02.1951/475
    - Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Africa - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/475.S
    - Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - East Africa Region, 1951; 02.1951/477
    - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/477.A
    - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - East Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/477.E
    - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - North Africa, 1951; 02.1951/485
    - North Africa - Administration, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3615)
    - North Africa - (A-H), 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3616)
    - North Africa - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617)
  - North Africa - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/485.A
  - unspecified, 02.1951/485.A-542
  - North Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/485.E
  - unspecified, 02.1951/485.E-542
  - Southern Africa, 1951; 02.1951/487
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
  - Southern Africa - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/487.A
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
  - Southern Africa - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/487.C
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
  - Southern Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/487.E
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
  - West Africa, 1951; 02.1951/495
    - West Africa Region, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3618)
  - France, 1951; 02.1951/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3619)
    - France - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3620)
    - France - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3621)
  - France - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/500.A
    - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/500.E
    - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - France - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/500.S
    - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - Vietnam, 1951; 02.1951/509
    - Vietnam, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - Society Islands, 1951; 02.1951/520
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Tahiti.
  - Asia, 1951; 02.1951/600
    - Asia, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3623)
    - Tahiti (Society Islands), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - China, 1951; 02.1951/601
    - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/601.E
    - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
  - China - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/601.R
    - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
  - Taiwan, 1951; 02.1951/605
    - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
  - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/605.A
    - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
  - Taiwan - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/605.C
    - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
  - Japan, 1951; 02.1951/609
    - Japan - (General) - Administration, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3626)
    - Japan - (A-I), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3627)
    - Japan - (J-M), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3628)
    - Japan - (N-P), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3629)
    - Japan - (Q-Z), 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3630)
  - Japan - Medical Science, 1951; 02.1951/609.A
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Japan - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/609.C
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/609.E
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/609.R
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Japan - Social Services, 1951; 02.1951/609.S
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Korea, 1951; 02.1951/613
    - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/613.E
    - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/613.R
    - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
  - Thailand, 1951; 02.1951/617
    - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/617.A
    - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Thailand - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/617.R
    - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Southeast Asia, 1951; 02.1951/625
    - Southeast Asia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Holland, 1951; 02.1951/650
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3634)
  - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/650.A
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Holland - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/650.C
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/650.E
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/650.R
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Holland - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/650.S
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Indonesia, 1951; 02.1951/652
    - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/652.E
    - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/652.R
    - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Europe, 1951; 02.1951/700
    - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
  - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/700.A
    - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
  - Europe - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/700.C
    - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
  - Europe - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/700.S
    - Dev-1 Devinney, Leland C. - Diary, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3637)
  - Afghanistan, 1951; 02.1951/703
    - Afghanistan, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria, 1951; 02.1951/705
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/705.A
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 02.1951/705.D
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/705.E
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/705.S
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium, 1951; 02.1951/707
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/707.A
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/707.C
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/707.R
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/707.S
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Yugoslavia, 1951; 02.1951/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
  - Yugoslavia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 02.1951/710.D
    - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
  - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/710.E
    - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
  - Yugoslavia - Public Health Education, 1951; 02.1951/710.L
    - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
  - Bulgaria, 1951; 02.1951/711
    - Bulgaria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1951; 02.1951/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Denmark, 1951; 02.1951/713
    - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Denmark - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/713.C
    - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/713.E
    - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Iceland, 1951; 02.1951/715
    - Iceland, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Iceland - Tuberculosis, 1951; 02.1951/715.T
    - Iceland, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Scandinavia, 1951; 02.1951/716
    - Scandinavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Germany, 1951; 02.1951/717
    - Germany - (General) - (A-G), 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3641)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3642)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3643)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3644)
    - Germany - Institute for International Educational Research, Frankfurt, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3668)
  - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/717.A
    - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 02.1951/717.D
    - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/717.E
    - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Germany - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/717.S
    - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Greece, 1951; 02.1951/749
    - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Greece - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/749.E
    - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Greece - Malaria, 1951; 02.1951/749.I
    - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Greece - Health Services, 1951; 02.1951/749.K
    - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Hungary, 1951; 02.1951/750
    - Hungary, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3646)
  - Italy, 1951; 02.1951/751
    - Italy - (A-P), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3647)
    - Italy - (Q-Z), 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3648)
  - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/751.A
    - Italy, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/751.E
    - Italy, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Norway, 1951; 02.1951/767
    - Norway, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/767.E
    - Norway, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Latvia, 1951; 02.1951/768
    - Latvia, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Iran, 1951; 02.1951/771
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran - Anglo-Iranian Oil Co., 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3669)
  - Iran - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/771.A
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
  - Iran - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/771.C
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
  - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/771.E
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
  - Iran - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/771.R
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3669)
  - Portugal, 1951; 02.1951/773
    - Portugal, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Portugal - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/773.C
    - Portugal, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Romania, 1951; 02.1951/783
    - Romania, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - USSR, 1951; 02.1951/785
    - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - USSR - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/785.C
    - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - USSR - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/785.E
    - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - USSR - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/785.S
    - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Poland, 1951; 02.1951/789
    - Poland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Spain, 1951; 02.1951/795
    - Spain, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Spain - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/795.E
    - Spain, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Sweden, 1951; 02.1951/800
    - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
  - Sweden - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/800.C
    - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
  - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/800.E
    - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
  - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/800.R
    - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
  - Switzerland, 1951; 02.1951/803
    - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
  - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/803.E
    - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
  - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/803.R
    - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
  - Near East Region, 1951; 02.1951/804
    - Near East, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey, 1951; 02.1951/805
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/805.C
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/805.E
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/805.R
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/805.S
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Israel, 1951; 02.1951/825
    - Israel, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3655)
  - Israel - Malaria, 1951; 02.1951/825.I
    - Israel, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3655)
  - Lebanon, 1951; 02.1951/833
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3656)
  - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1951; 02.1951/833.A
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
  - Lebanon - Nursing, 1951; 02.1951/833.C
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
  - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 02.1951/833.E
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
  - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 02.1951/833.R
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)